<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FoodFast</string>
    <string name="receta_salmon">Ingredients: Salmon fillet, carrots, broccoli, olive oil, lemon, salt and pepper.  Directions: Season salmon with salt, pepper and lemon juice. Place on a baking sheet along with carrots and broccoli. Drizzle with olive oil and bake until the salmon is cooked and the vegetables are tender.</string>
    <string name="receta_pasta">Ingredients: Wholemeal pasta, fresh spinach, pine nuts, garlic, olive oil, Parmesan cheese, salt and pepper. Instructions: Cook pasta as directed. Meanwhile, mix spinach, pine nuts, garlic, olive oil and Parmesan cheese ina blender to make the pesto.Mix the pesto with the cooked pasta.</string>
    <string name="receta_avena">Ingredients: Oatmeal, milk (or water), fresh fruits (such as bananas or strawberries), dried fruit (nuts or almonds), honey (optional) Instructions: Cook oatmeal according to package directions.  Serve with fresh fruit slices, dried fruit and a drizzle of honey if desired.</string>
    <string name="receta_ensaladapollo">Ingredients:  Grilled Chicken Breast  mixed lettuce, tomato, avocado, corn, cilantro-lime dressing.  Instructions:  Cut the chicken into strips.  Mix with the salad ingredients and dress with the cilantro-lime dressing.</string>
    <string name="recera_omelette">Ingredients:  Eggs  Fresh spinach  Cheese (can be feta cheese or your choice)  salt and pepper to taste.  Instructions:  Sauté the spinach in a frying pan until wilted.  Beat in the eggs, add salt and pepper to taste, pour over the spinach and cook until firm.  Add the cheese on top and fold the omelet over.</string>
    <string name="receta_quinoa">Ingredients:  Quinoa  courgette  Peppers  Mushrooms  onion  olive oil  garlic  salt and pepper.  Instructions:  Cook quinoa as directed.  In a frying pan, sauté the garlic vegetables in olive oil until tender.  Mix the vegetables with the quinoa.</string>
    <string name="receta_pupusa">Ingredients: 2 cups of corn flour 1-1.5 cups of warm water 1 cup of grated cheese (preferably quesillo) Filling options: pork rinds, refried beans, cheese Instructions: In a bowl, mix the corn flour with the warm water. Knead until you obtain a soft and malleable dough. Form small balls with the dough. With your finger, make a hole in each ball and fill it with the ingredient of your choice (chicharrón, beans, cheese). Close the dough around the filling and form a kind of flat disc. In a hot skillet or griddle, cook the pupusas on both sides until they are golden brown and cooked through.</string>
    <string name="receta_sopares">Ingredients: 500 g beef (preferably bone-in) 1 yuca cut into pieces 2 corn, cut into slices 2 carrots sliced 2 potatoes cut into pieces 1 green banana cut into pieces 1 chopped green chili 1 chopped onion 2 cloves of garlic, minced Coriander leaves Salt and pepper to taste  Instructions: In a large pot, boil the beef with enough water until tender. Add the yuca, corn, carrots, potatoes and banana to the pot. In a separate skillet, sauté the chili, onion and garlic until golden brown and add to the pot. Cook over medium heat until all the vegetables are tender and the flavors blend. Add salt, pepper and cilantro to taste before serving.</string>
    <string name="receta_enchiladas">ingredients: 12 corn tortillas 2 cups shredded chicken 2 cups shredded cabbage 1 cup tomato sauce 1 cup of grated cheese 1 chopped onion Vegetable oil Sour cream and avocado to serve (optional)  Instructions: Lightly fry the tortillas in hot oil and drain them on absorbent paper to remove excess fat. In a separate pan, mix the chicken with the tomato sauce and heat it. Place a portion of chicken in each tortilla and roll them up. Top the enchiladas with shredded cabbage, grated cheese and chopped onion. Serve the enchiladas with sour cream and avocado if desired.</string>
    <string name="receta_panespollo">Ingredients:  1 turkey breast 4 cups chicken broth 2 carrots cut into pieces 2 potatoes cut into pieces 1 chayote cut into pieces 1 corn, cut into slices 1/2 cup peas 1 chopped onion 2 cloves of garlic, minced 1/4 cup chopped cilantro 6 French breads (bolillos) or similar breads  Instructions: Boil the turkey breast in the chicken broth until cooked. Then, crumble it. In a large pot, add the shredded beef, carrots, potatoes, chayote, corn and peas to the turkey cooking broth.  Cook until the vegetables are tender. In a separate skillet, sauté onion and garlic until golden.  Add them to the pot along with the cilantro. Cut the loaves in half, without completely separating the two halves. Place a portion of the turkey and vegetable mixture inside each bun.</string>
    <string name="receta_text">INGREDIENTS</string>
    <string name="receta_tamales">Ingredients: 2 cups of corn flour 1 cup lard or vegetable lard 1 cup chicken broth 1/2 cup peas 1 grated carrot 1 red pepper chopped 1 chopped green chili 1/2 cup cooked and drained chickpeas 12 banana leaves (or corn husks) clean and dry Salt to taste  Instructions: In a large bowl, mix the cornflour with the butter until well incorporated. Gradually add the chicken broth until you have a soft, pliable dough. Add the peas, carrot, pepper, chili and chickpeas to the dough. Mix well. Spread a banana leaf and place a portion of dough in the center. Wrap the dough with the sheet, folding the ends to form a packet. Steam the tamales for approximately 1.5-2 hours or until the dough is firm.</string>
    <string name="cuenta">Account</string>
    <string name="usuario">User:</string>
    <string name="contrase_a">Password:</string>
    <string name="ajustes">Settings</string>
    <string name="preguntas_frecuentes">Frequent questions</string>
    <string name="cerrar_sesi_n">Sign off</string>
    <string name="cerrar_la_app">Close the app</string>
    <string name="a_adir">Add</string>
    <string name="nombre_de_la_receta">Recipe name:</string>
    <string name="ingredientes">Ingredients</string>
    <string name="tiempo_de_comida">Food time</string>
    <string name="instrucciones">Instructions</string>
    <string name="agregar_receta">Add Recipe</string>
    <string name="agregar_imagen">Add Image</string>
    <string name="iniciar_sesi_n">Log in</string>
    <string name="nombre_de_usuario">Username</string>
    <string name="contrase_a1">Password</string>
    <string name="recuerda_mis_datos">Remember my details</string>
    <string name="iniciar_sesi_n3">LOG IN</string>
    <string name="no_tienes_una_cuenta">You do not have an account?</string>
    <string name="registrarse">CHECK IN</string>
    <string name="recetas">Recipes</string>
    <string name="salm_n_al_horno">Baked salmon</string>
    <string name="pasta_integral">Wheat pasta</string>
    <string name="ensalada_de_pollo">Chicken salad</string>
    <string name="omelette_de_espinacas">Spinach omelette</string>
    <string name="avena">Oatmeal</string>
    <string name="quinoa_con_verduras">Quinoa with Vegetables</string>
    <string name="pupusas">PUPUSAS</string>
    <string name="sopa_de_res">SOPA DE RES</string>
    <string name="enchiladas">ENCHILADAS</string>
    <string name="tamales">TAMALES</string>
    <string name="panes_con_pollo">PANES CON POLLO</string>
    <string name="almuerzos">Lunches</string>
    <string name="ensalada_de_pollo2">Chicken salad</string>
    <string name="sopa_de_res2">BEEF SOUP</string>
    <string name="pasta_integral2">Wheat pasta</string>
    <string name="cenas">Dinners</string>
    <string name="quinoa_con_verduras2">Quinoa with Vegetables</string>
    <string name="salm_n_al_horno2">Baked salmon</string>
    <string name="enchiladas2">Enchiladas</string>
    <string name="desayunos">Breakfasts</string>
    <string name="avena2">Oatmeal</string>
    <string name="omelette_de_espinacas2">Spinach omelette</string>
    <string name="pupusas2">Pupusas</string>
    <string name="preguntas_frecuentes2">Frequent questions</string>
    <string name="c_mo_puedo_buscar_una_receta_espec_fica_en_la_aplicaci_n">How can I search for a specific recipe in the app?</string>
    <string name="para_buscar_una_receta_simplemente_haz_clic_en_la_opci_n_buscar_en_la_barra_de_navegaci_n">To search for a recipe, simply click the Search option in the navigation bar.</string>
    <string name="c_mo_a_ado_una_nueva_receta_a_la_aplicaci_n">How do I add a new recipe to the app?</string>
    <string name="para_a_adir_una_nueva_receta_selecciona_la_opci_n_a_adir_en_la_barra_de_navegaci_n">To add a new recipe, select the Add option in the navigation bar</string>
    <string name="c_mo_puedo_proporcionar_retroalimentaci_n_sobre_la_aplicaci_n">How can I provide feedback on the application?</string>
    <string name="nos_encantar_a_recibir_tus_comentarios_dir_gete_a_la_secci_n_ajustes_y_selecciona_cont_ctanos_ah_encontrar_s_formas_de_contactarnos">We would love to receive your comments. Go to the Settings section and select Contact Us, there you will find ways to contact us.</string>
    <string name="registrarse2">Check in</string>
    <string name="nombre_de_usuario2">Username</string>
    <string name="contrase_a2">Password</string>
    <string name="se_recomienda_una_contrase_a_segura_y_f_cil_de_recordar">A strong, easy-to-remember password is recommended.</string>
    <string name="registrarse3">Check in</string>
    <string name="ya_tienes_una_cuenta">Do you already have an account?</string>
    <string name="iniciar_sesi_n4">Log in</string>
    <string name="categor_as">CATEGORIES</string>
    <string name="desayunos2">Breakfasts</string>
    <string name="almuerzos2">Lunches</string>
    <string name="cenas2">Dinners</string>
    <string name="receta3">Recipe</string>
    <string name="avena_con_frutas3">Oatmeal with fruits</string>
    <string name="aporte_de">Contribution of</string>
    <string name="calificaci_n">Qualification</string>
    <string name="receta5">Recipe</string>
    <string name="ensalda_de_pollo2">Chicken Salad</string>
    <string name="aporte_de2">Contribution of</string>
    <string name="calificaci_n2">Qualification</string>
    <string name="omelette_de_espinacas3">Spinach omelette</string>
    <string name="aporte_de3">Contribution of</string>
    <string name="pasta_integral4">Wheat pasta</string>
    <string name="quinoa_con_verduras3">Quinoa with Vegetables</string>
    <string name="salm_n_al_horno3">Baked salmon</string>
    <string name="sopa_de_res3">Beef soup</string>
    <string name="panes_con_pollo3">Bread with Chiken</string>
    <string name="pupusas3">Pupusas</string>
    <string name="sopa_de_res4">Sopa de Res</string>
    <string name="tamales3">Tamales</string>
</resources>